(Penny:)I can't believe
you're seeing someone
(Penny:)and we don't even know about it.
(Bernadette:)Yeah, why wouldn't
you tell us?
(Amy:)Because it's new and weird
(Amy:)and I'm just trying
to figure it all out.
(Amy:)And I knew
(Amy:)if I told you guys
I had been out
(Amy:)with a few people that you'd get
way too excited about it.
(Stuart:)A few people?
What?!
Amy! - Amy!
(Stuart:)So, are we allowed to ask
how it's going?
(Amy:)It's going fine.
(Amy:)It's mostly just been
meeting people for coffee.
Wha...?!
(Raj:)I thought we
were all...
(Raj:)Never mind.
I-I thought you
weren't ready
(Bernadette:)to start seeing people.
(Amy:)Well, I don't have
much experience dating,
(Amy:)so I decided
it would be good for me
(Amy:)to, you know,
get out there a little.
(Penny:)Well, good for you.
(Sheldon:)Thank you.
(Bernadette:)And how many guys
have you gone out with?
(Stuart:)Please be less than two.
(Man:)Three.
Damn it.
(Sheldon:)Well, the Swedes
might beat us,
(Sheldon:)but at least we won't get
gang-noogied in prison.